<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Infrafrequency</title><link href="http://sebastiantorrente.github.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://sebastiantorrente.github.com/feeds/Blog.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://sebastiantorrente.github.com/</id><updated>2013-03-20T09:13:00+00:00</updated><entry><title>There we go.</title><link href="http://sebastiantorrente.github.com/wego.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-03-20T09:13:00+00:00</updated><author><name>Sebastian Torrente</name></author><id>tag:sebastiantorrente.github.com,2013-03-20:wego.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#8217;s been, well, almost two weeks since I touched this. The problems to deploy this on GitHub pages put this project in the backburner. I know, I know, is supposed to be easy, and I&amp;#8217;m sure it is. But it seems that there is something glaringly obvious that I don&amp;#8217;t see right&amp;nbsp;now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, there is a lot to do and right now I don&amp;#8217;t have an internet connection, so I&amp;#8217;ve been studying a lot and preparing for a job interview. It&amp;#8217;s an interesting one, hope everything goes well. And about studying, a lot of Python mainly, with a little bit of Vim, emacs and MySQL on the&amp;nbsp;side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, and because I have no internet I played Megaman 2. Other that the life toll in some stages is a nice game. Spent a lot of money in coffee too, to get some&amp;nbsp;internet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So far so good, time to read my notes for the interview again, iron my shirt and make that tie know. Wish me&amp;nbsp;luck.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="blog"></category><category term="dailylife"></category></entry><entry><title>Example post</title><link href="http://sebastiantorrente.github.com/example1.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-03-05T11:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>Sebastian Torrente</name></author><id>tag:sebastiantorrente.github.com,2013-03-05:example1.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;We require 3 research interns to work in the exciting world of venture capital. Interns will research information on global venture capital funds from databases, websites, industry reports, the financial press and direct telephone contact with senior venture capital&amp;nbsp;investors. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interns will build and manage a global investor network using social media marketing techniques. Interns will also write summary reports on venture capital funds for publication on the&amp;nbsp;website. &lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="blog"></category><category term="dailylife"></category><category term="example"></category></entry><entry><title>Arrival</title><link href="http://sebastiantorrente.github.com/arrival.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-03-03T15:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>Sebastian Torrente</name></author><id>tag:sebastiantorrente.github.com,2013-03-03:arrival.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Now that I moved to London to get a life, I guess is time to break my &amp;#8216;nothing to say, no sense to open a blog&amp;#8217; policy and make one. I have friends who&amp;#8217;d like to know about me after all. Is also a way to keep track of things, practice my writting and in the technical side of things, getting some fun with the tweaking of the&amp;nbsp;blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Truth be told, I wanted to open a blog but never found the right tool to do it. Yeah, there are things like Wordpress and Blogspot. And hey, they are fine choices. But I wanted something a little bit more tricky. The kind of thing that would give me fun in a &amp;#8220;let&amp;#8217;s make it work my way&amp;#8221; way. And Pelican was the perfect choice. Uses git as a way to make new posts, will force me to learn things like Markdown and the blogs made with it look clean. Being able to use emacs or Vim as tools to write my posts is also a good&amp;nbsp;plus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And nothing more to say so far. I&amp;#8217;ll try to add comments as soon as I can. Until them, there are some cover letters to write and a Linkedin profile to&amp;nbsp;update.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you later, and take&amp;nbsp;care.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="blog"></category><category term="dailylife"></category></entry></feed>